#### Contact

mhaburealh@msn.com

www.linkedin.com/in/mohammed-abu-realh-5286a74b (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Microsoft Excel Microsoft Office PowerPoint

# Mohammed Abu Realh

CNO Hospital Based Services, (ANE) Cook County Hospital and Health System

Greater Chicago Area

# Summary

Experienced executive of Nursing Services with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Research, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft PowerPoint, Hospitals, and Healthcare. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master of Science of Nursing focused in Nursing Administration from George Mason University.

# Experience

Cook County Health and Hospitals System Chief Nursing Officer Hospital Based Services October 2017 - Present (2 years 10 months)

Greater Chicago Area

University of Maryland Charles Reginal Medical Center Director Of Nursing Services June 2012 - July 2017 (5 years 2 months) La Plata, Maryland

Providence Hospital (Providence Health System) Senior Director of Nursing September 2004 - March 2012 (7 years 7 months) Washington D.C. Metro Area

### Education

George Mason University

Master of Science of Nursing, Nursing Administration · (1994 - 1996)